=== PAWS - Canvas Child-Theme with Canvas Advanced Addons Class - Extended ===
 
All functionality pertaining to the dashboard widget feature.
 
package WordPress
subpackage Canvas_Advanced_Addons_Extended
category Plugin
author Stuart Duff, Boris Uhlig for PAWS International
Donate link: http://stuartduff.com/, http://www.paws-int.com
Tags: themes, addon, styling, woothemes, canvas
Requires at least: 3.5
Tested up to: 3.5.2
Stable tag: 1.6.0 - Light
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

== Description ==

The PAWS Canvas Child-Themewith Canvas Advanced Addons - Extended will add additonal styling and customizations options to the WooThemes 
Framework / Theme Options Panel of you Canvas v5 theme.

NOTE: This Child-Theme is not supported by WooThemes and if you require support please ask in the support section of PAWS International 
specifically relating to this Child-Theme.

This Canvas Child Theme is based on the originally by Stuart Duff developed class "canvas-advanced-addons" and add's further useful and most 
requested functions and elements to your Canvas Theme.

This Child Theme has been developed for the website of PAWS International (http://www.paws-int.com), the new non-profit umbrella organization, 
which is aiming to unite pet & animal welfare activist, shelters & rescues all over the world under one roof, to streamline activities and 
jointly work to stop cruelty to animals, back-yard breeding, supporting shelters and special needs animals. Wordpress and PHP Experts volunteered 
and devoted their time free of charge to develop the Canvas PAWS Child-Theme, aiming to request you to become a donor in return for using this 
Child-Theme partially and/or complete.

Check it out in action at http://www.paws-int.com

Thank you in advance for your donation.

Some of the features the Child-Theme & Plugin adds to your Canvas theme are listed below.

== Features == All features can be selectively enabled or disabled!

 1. Display full width header with colour controls and background image settings.
 2. Display full width footer with colour controls and background image settings.
 3. Adjust The Primary Navigation Menu Items Position Left, Right, Center.
 4. Adjust The Top Navigation Menu Items Position Left, Right, Center.
 5. Add theme connect & subscribe section social icons to the header area.
 6. Add business slider to homepage.
 7. Add magazine slider to homepage.
 8. Display page content below the magazine slider.
 9. Move WooCommerce cart to top or primary menu thanks to [Gerhard Potgieter] (https://github.com/kloon).
10. Add Social Icons to Header or into Navigation and adjust Position Left, Right
11. Add Search Form to into Navigation Position Right
12. Move Logo from Header into Navigation 
13. Add "Login/Logout" to Top-Menu or Primary-Menu
14. Add WPML Language Flag only to Top-Menu
15. Add Shortcode Support to Widgets
16. Modify the Tag-Cloud Settings: Fontsize (min/max), Number of Tags to display
17. Add Open Graph Function to Website to 
18. Move jquery into Footer
19. Activate Responsive Meta Tags
20. Activate Viewport Meta Tags for Mobile Devices
21. Adding additional Widget area in Header: Position Left & Right
22. Removing Canvas Top-Ad 
23. Adding two additional Navigation Menus to place in i.e. in Footer
24. Use Twitter Bootstrap Icons instead of Canvas default icons 

== Plugin-Support ==

This PAWS Canvas Child-Theme is designed to integrate the following Third-Party Plugins, but will also work without them:
A request: Please use the mentioned links, so that for a potential purchase the earned Affiliate fee will be donated to PAWS International! Thank you!

1. WP Bakery - Visual Composer - (http://codecanyon.net/item/visual-composer-for-wordpress/242431?ref=buhlig) 
2. UberMenu - WordPress Mega Menu Plugin - (http://codecanyon.net/item/ubermenu-wordpress-mega-menu-plugin/154703?ref=buhlig)
3. Slider Revolution Responsive WordPress Plugin -  (http://codecanyon.net/item/slider-revolution-responsive-wordpress-plugin/2751380?ref=buhlig)
4. WPML -The WordPress Multilingual Plugin - (http://wpml.org)

The following plugins (Pro/Full Versions) have been donated by it's respected developers:
1. Connections - (http://connections-pro.com/) - Thank you Steven Zahm 
2. Social Login - (http://www.oneall.com) - Thank you Claude Schlesser

Further the following Third-Party Plugins (extract) are used by PAWS International with Woothemes Canvas and this Child-Theme:

1. Advanced Menu Widget - (http://wordpress.org/plugins/advanced-menu-widget/)
2. Enhanced Text Widget - (http://wordpress.org/plugins/enhanced-text-widget/)
3. Flexi Pages Widget - (http://wordpress.org/plugins/flexi-pages-widget/)
4. ShowBiz - (http://codecanyon.net/item/showbiz-business-carousel-jquery-plugin/926348?ref=buhlig)
5. Simple Tags - (http://wordpress.org/plugins/simple-tags/)
6. Stortcodes - Ultimate - (http://wordpress.org/plugins/shortcodes-ultimate/)

== Installation ==

1. Make sure you have Woothemes Canvas (at least Version 5.3.0) installed
2. Download the Child-Theme 
3. Upload the ZIP file through the "Themes > Add New > Upload" screen in your WordPress dashboard.
4. Activate the Child-Theme through the 'Themes' menu in WordPress
5. Access the features from the WooThemes Options Panel > PAWS Settings

== Screenshots ==

1. The Canvas Advanced Addons Menu View.

= 1.6.0 - light =
* Intial Version.